Faculty Reference; Collection ua950.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- W, 1851-2005; 23
  - Werner, Alfred C., Undated (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Werner, Cindy, Undated (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Werner, Michael R., Undated (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Wertz, Marjorie D., Undated (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Weseman, Mary Lou, Undated (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Wesser, Robert, Undated (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Wesser, Robert F., Undated (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Wessman, James W., Undated (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Westbrook, Perry, Undated (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Westbrook, Perry, Undated (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Westcott, Joan Bartlett, Undated (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Westervelt, Gary W., Undated (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Weston, Moran, Undated (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Whalen, Jean, Undated (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Whalen, Lucille, Undated (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Wharton, Clifton R., Jr., 1970 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Wharton, Clifton R., Jr., Undated (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Wharton, Clifton R., Jr., Undated (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Wheeler, Linda, Undated (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Wheeler, Paul Frank, Undated (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Wheeler, Paul F., 1961 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Wheeler, Paul F., Undated (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Whitaker, Judith, Undated (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Whitaker, Judith Gage, Undated (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Whitbeck, Caroline, Undated (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Whitby, Robert, Undated (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - White, Cara A., Undated (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - White, Dan, Undated (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - White, Gary W., Undated (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - White, James L., Undated (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - White, Jeanne, Undated (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - White, Ronald K., Undated (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Whitford, Richard, Undated (Box 44, Folder 70)
  - Whitlock, Donald A., Undated (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Whitney, Willard Hall, Undated (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Whittaker, Carol, Undated (Box 44, Folder 73)
  - Whittaker, Tatyana I., Undated (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - Whitten, William B., Undated (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - Wick-Petller, Joan, Undated (Box 44, Folder 76)
  - Widom, Cathy Spatz, Undated (Box 44, Folder 77)
  - Widom, Cathy Spatz, Undated (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - Wiest, Nailene Chou, Undated (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - Wilbanks, William, Undated (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - Wilbur, W. Allan, Undated (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - Wilcox, Kevin, Undated (Box 44, Folder 82)
  - Wilder, Laura A., Undated (Box 44, Folder 83)
  - Wilder, Margaret, Undated (Box 44, Folder 84)
  - Wildove, Howard, Undated (Box 44, Folder 85)
  - Wiles, David K., Undated (Box 44, Folder 86)
  - Wiles, David K., Undated (Box 44, Folder 87)
  - Wiley, Frank J., Undated (Box 44, Folder 88)
  - Wilke, Richard, Undated (Box 44, Folder 89)
  - Wilken, Donald R., Undated (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Wilken, Donald R., Undated (Box 44, Folder 91)
  - Wilken, Donald R., Undated (Box 44, Folder 92)
  - Wilkie, Richard, Undated (Box 44, Folder 93)
  - Wilkie, Richard W., Undated (Box 44, Folder 94)
  - Wilkins, Leslie T., Undated (Box 44, Folder 95)
  - Wilkins, Leslie T., Undated (Box 44, Folder 96)
  - Wilkinson, Jean (Foster) H., Undated (Box 44, Folder 97)
  - Wilkinson, Richard G., Undated (Box 44, Folder 98)
  - Willard, Dan E., Undated (Box 44, Folder 99)
  - Williams, Catherine, Undated (Box 44, Folder 100)
  - Williams, Charles R., Undated (Box 44, Folder 101)
  - Williams-Myers, A.J., Undated (Box 44, Folder 102)
  - Williams, Fannie B., Undated (Box 44, Folder 103)
  - Williams, Geoffrey, Undated (Box 44, Folder 104)
  - Williams, James R., Undated (Box 44, Folder 105)
  - Williams, James R., Undated (Box 44, Folder 106)
  - Williams, Juan, Undated (Box 44, Folder 107)
  - Willaims, Kevin, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Williams, Lillian Serece, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Lois Virginia, 1948-1979 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Williams, Marianne, Undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Williams, P.F., Undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Sara, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Sara, Undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Williams, Sara, Undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Shana, Undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Williams, Stacey, Undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Williams, Tracey, Undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Williamson, Ella Kisha, Undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Williamson, Wanda, Undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Wills, David, Undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Willsey, Warren, Undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Wilsey, Neal, Undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Wilson, Chris, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Wilson, Jamar, Undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Wilson, Karen, Undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Wilson, J. Nancy, Undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Wilson, William, Undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Wilson, William H., Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Winarsky, Norman D., Undated (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Windham, Douglas M., Undated (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Wing, Judith G., Undated (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Winkelman, John, Undated (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Winkelman, John, Undated (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Winkler, Wm. S., 1968 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Winn, Hudson, Undated (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Winn, Hudson Sumner, Undated (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Winn, Mary Beth, Undated (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Winn, Thomas, Undated (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Winstein, Allen, Undated (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Wint, Claudia, Undated (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Winter, Gene, Undated (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Winter, Kate, Undated (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Winters, William G., Undated (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Wissel, Peter A., Undated (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Wittenborg, Karen, Undated (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Wittowski, Wolfgang, Undated (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Wittowski, Wolfgang, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Wittner, Lawrence S., Undated (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Woefel, Joseph D., Undated (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Wolfe, Barbara, Undated (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Wolfe, Cary, Undated (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Wolfe, Douglas A., Undated (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Wolfe, Mark, Undated (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Wolff, John T., Undated (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Wolfran, Katherine, Undated (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Woo, Louis K., Undated (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Wood, Ann L., Undated (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - Wood, Ann L., Undated (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - Wood, Gary, Undated (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Wood, Harry, Undated (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - Wood, Starr, Undated (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - Woodbury, John R., Undated (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - Woolsworth, Samuel B., Undated (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - Wolpav, Jonathan, Undated (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - Word, Paul, Undated (Box 45, Folder 59)
  - Worden, Alissa Pollitz, Undated (Box 45, Folder 60)
  - Worden, Robert, Undated (Box 45, Folder 61)
  - Woroboff, David J., Undated (Box 45, Folder 62)
  - Wright, Cyprian, Undated (Box 45, Folder 63)
  - Wright, Elizabethada A., Undated (Box 45, Folder 64)
  - Wright, Gary A., Undated (Box 45, Folder 65)
  - Wright, Gary A., Undated (Box 45, Folder 66)
  - Wright, J. Ward, Undated (Box 45, Folder 67)
  - Wright, Leonard, Undated (Box 45, Folder 68)
  - Wright, Nathan Jr., Undated (Box 45, Folder 69)
  - Wright, Nathan Jr., Undated (Box 45, Folder 70)
  - Wright, Theodore, Undated (Box 45, Folder 71)
  - Wright, Theodore, Undated (Box 45, Folder 72)
  - Wu, Chuntao, Undated (Box 45, Folder 73)
  - Wulfert, Edelgard (Elga), Undated (Box 45, Folder 74)
  - Wulff, Daniel L., Undated (Box 45, Folder 75)
  - Wundt, Charles, Undated (Box 45, Folder 76)
  - Wygel, Maryann Murray, Undated (Box 45, Folder 77)
- X, 2004-2005; 24
  - Xu, Bai, 2004-2005 (Box 45, Folder 78)
  - Xu, Bai, 2004-2005 (Box 45, Folder 78)
- Y, 1851-2005; 25
  - Yadegari, Mohammad, Undated (Box 45, Folder 79)
  - Yalkut, Carolyn, Undated (Box 45, Folder 80)
  - Yang, Chung Shu, Undated (Box 45, Folder 81)
  - Yeaton, Kelly, Undated (Box 45, Folder 82)
  - Yencha, Andrew J., Undated (Box 45, Folder 83)
  - Yerburgh, Mark, Undated (Box 45, Folder 84)
  - Yerburgh, Mark R., Undated (Box 45, Folder 85)
  - Yoels, William C., Undated (Box 45, Folder 86)
  - Yogelski, Robert, Undated (Box 45, Folder 87)
  - Yohalem, Francoise, Undated (Box 45, Folder 88)
  - Yokoyama, Elaine Itsuko, Undated (Box 45, Folder 89)
  - York, George Morell, 1916-1947 (Box 45, Folder 90)
  - York, G.M., Undated (Box 45, Folder 91)
  - York, George H., Undated (Box 45, Folder 92)
  - York, Jeffrey (Jeff), Undated (Box 45, Folder 93)
  - York, Roy, Undated (Box 45, Folder 94)
  - Youmans, Kristen, Undated (Box 45, Folder 95)
  - Young, Michael, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 96)
  - Young, Samuel, Undated (Box 45, Folder 97)
  - Young, William F., Undated (Box 45, Folder 98)
  - Young, William F., Undated (Box 45, Folder 99)
  - Young, Yuchi, Undated (Box 45, Folder 100)
  - Yu, Li-hua, Undated (Box 45, Folder 101)
  - Yuki, Gary, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 102)
  - Yukl, Gary, Undated (Box 45, Folder 103)
  - Yum, June Ock, Undated (Box 45, Folder 104)
  - Yun, Kwan Koo, Undated (Box 45, Folder 105)
  - Yurkewecz, Tom, Undated (Box 45, Folder 106)
  - Yuter, Alan J., Undated (Box 45, Folder 107)
- Z, 1851-2005; 26
  - Zacek, Joseph F., Undated (Box 45, Folder 108)
  - Zacek, Joseph F., Undated (Box 45, Folder 109)
  - Zacharias, Jerrold R., Undated (Box 45, Folder 110)
  - Zack, Naomi, Undated (Box 45, Folder 111)
  - Zahavi, Gerald, Undated (Box 45, Folder 112)
  - Zahavi, Gerald, Undated (Box 45, Folder 113)
  - Zahazi, Jerry, Undated (Box 45, Folder 114)
  - Zahm, Norbert, Undated (Box 45, Folder 115)
  - Zai, Liang, Undated (Box 45, Folder 116)
  - Zak, Albin J., Undated (Box 45, Folder 117)
  - Zaloom, Edward, Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Zauber, Raisa, Undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Zausner, Meryl, Undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Zazzau, Vivien, Undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Zazzau, Vivien E., ca. 2002-2010 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Zeh, Robert M., Undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Zeigler, Bernard, Undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Zelizer, Julian E., Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Zeller, Phil, Undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Zendle, Hal, Undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Zenner, Walter Paul, Undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Zenzen, Edmund J., Undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Zetka, James R., Undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Zilles, Luke, Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Zimmerman, Barry J., Undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph, Undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph, Undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph, Undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph, Undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph, Undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Zimmerman, Joesph F., Undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Zimmerman, Joesph F., Undated (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Zimmerman, Peter, Undated (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Zimmerman, Sanford, Undated (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Zimmerman, Virrgil, 1914-2001 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Zimmermann, Virgil B., Undated (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Zimmers, Karen, Undated (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Zitomer, Richard, Undated (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Zubieta, Jon, Undated (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Zubrick, James, Undated (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Zuckerman, Jerold J., Undated (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Zumbolo, Anthony, Undated (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Zwana, Japhet M., Undated (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Zwana, Japhet M., Undated (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Zwarich, Ronald J., Undated (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Zych, Maria, Undated (Box 46, Folder 42)